konstruktor.com 2015-02-21

# 

PRIVACY POLICY
Konstruktor US Lab, LLC, its website and application ("we," "our" or "us") believe that
your privacy is very important. This Policy outlines the types of personally identifiable
information and other data that we will collect from you through the website and
applications we provide ("Websites/Apps"), and how we will use and when we might
disclose such information and data to third parties. Your installation and/or use of these
Website/Application and/or submission of information to us constitute your consent to
this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective as of November 1, 2014.
There are two types of information we may collect through your use of the
Website/Application:
1. "Personal Information" which is the type of information that can specifically be linked
to you personally, such as your full name, physical address, email address, telephone
number, photograph, location, credit card information and, in some cases, user names;
and
2. Non-personal "Usage Data" which is anonymous data about your use of the
Websites/Apps that is tied to your computer and/or device through which you use the
Websites/Apps.
Personal Information and Usage Data That We Collect and How We Collect It
• If you choose to open an account with us, we may collect your name, email address,
        date of birth and physical address.
• If you choose to connect to one of our Website/Application through a third-party, we
        may collect Personal Information from your profile on such third-party, such as
        your name, username, and photograph.
• If you choose to make a purchase through our Website/Application, we will collect
        your credit card information and other billing information.
• If you choose to make use of any public forum, comment section, or chat function, we
        may collect any Personal Information you may disclose through such means.
• If you choose to send a message to another user or defined group of users through our
        message, chat, post or other in-game function, we may collect any Personal
        Information you may disclose through such means, as well as the necessary
        Personal Information of the user(s) you are contacting, in order to facilitate the
        communication (Note: we will never collect any information sent outside of the
        functionality of our Website/Application, including through emails or text
        messages).
• If you choose to submit your Personal Information to us for any other reason in any
        other form, we will collect such Personal Information and use it for the purposes
        for which you submitted it.
• We may collect the following Usage Data when you make use of the

        Website/Application: your computer's IP address, your mobile phone's unique
        device ID or other persistent identifiers, geolocation information, your device's
        software platform and firmware, the type of browser you use, the date and time of
        your use of our Website/Application, the actions you take within the
        Website/Application.
We will not collect any Personal Information from you simply by virtue of your visiting
our Website; we only collect it if you choose to submit it to us. You represent and
warrant that all Personal Information you provide us is true and correct and relates to you
and not to any other person.
Use of the Personal Information and Usage Data That We Collect
We will use your Personal Information to provide you with any goods, services, or
functionality you've requested or respond to any inquiries you've made. We may also use
your Personal Information in order to contact you to promote our Websites/Apps,
contests and any specials we may offer. In the event that we send you advertising or
marketing materials, we will provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving
such materials in the future. You may also opt-out of receiving such materials at any time
in accordance with the instructions provided in this Privacy Policy.
Usage Data may be used by us for administrative, analytical, research, optimization,
security and other purposes. Specifically, we may use your Usage Data to help us learn
more about your gaming activities, personalize your content, compile statistics, respond
to customer service inquiries, provide security and to otherwise enhance your gaming
experience. Usage Data may also be used to help us provide you advertising that better
suits your interests. Geolocation information will be used to determine the jurisdiction in
which you're located so we can determine what set of laws apply to you. Your device ID
may be used so we can send you push notifications (if you choose to allow that function)
and track your use of our Website/Application so that we can better understand your
preferences and tendencies which will help us best personalize your experience and
provide you with in-game offers and notifications that are tailored to you.
Disclosure of the Personal Information and Usage Data That We Collect
Konstruktor is a global company with offices and entities around the world. We may
transfer your Personal Information and Usage Data to our other entities, but such
information shall continue to be governed by this Privacy Policy.
We will not sell, rent or transfer your Personal Information to third parties, except as
otherwise indicated herein. We will not store your credit card information. In order to
process credit card payments, we will use the service of a secure, third-party credit card
processor.

We use the services of third parties who will have limited access to your Personal
Information to be used for specific purposes. These purposes may include credit card
processing, prize delivery, marketing assistance, customer service, and data analysis. The
third parties we contract with for these purposes will be authorized to use your Personal
Information only for the purposes for which the party was engaged. In addition, Usage
Data in aggregated, anonymous form may be shared with third parties who assist us with
our internal operations such as administration, analytics, research, and optimization.
We may disclose your Personal Information or other information collected if required by
law or court order, if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct, to
investigate and/or take action against illegal activity, suspected abuse or unauthorized use
of the Website/Application, or to protect the property or safety of others.
In connection with any sale of our company or any line of business (including the assets
relating thereto), customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets,
and such customer information (including your Personal Information) will be transferred
or sold to the acquirer in the event of any such sale or disposition of any or all of our
business.
Credit Card Transactions
If you choose to purchase a product from our Website/Application, you represent and
warrant that all credit card information you provide will be accurate and correct and that
you are authorized to use such credit card. In no event will you provide us with any false
or fraudulent information.
Your Rights
We ask that you keep the Personal Information that you provide to us current and that
you correct any information you have provided us by contacting us at
privatepolicy@konstruktor.com.
If you wish to opt out of further communications from us, or if you wish to review, delete
and/or revise the Personal Information we have stored about you, please contact us with
your specific requests at privatepolicy@konstruktor.com; provided, however, that we
reserve the right to retain an archive of such Personal Information for a commercially
reasonable time to ensure that its deletion does not affect the integrity of our data and we
further reserve the right to retain an anonymous version of such information.
If you use the Website/Application, you are responsible for maintaining the
confidentiality of your account and for restricting access to your computer or device, and
you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account.

Partnerships and External Sources
Our Website/Application may link to external sites beyond our control. This privacy
policy covers only the way we treat the Personal Information and Usage Data we collect
on our Website/Application. By accessing any external sites, you are agreeing to the
privacy policies of those sites. Please understand that the external sites may have
different policies with respect to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal
Information. We have no control over and are not responsible for the privacy practices of
such third parties. Therefore, you are encouraged to review the privacy policies of all
third-party Website/Application. Without limiting anything in the following section, we
are not liable in any way for the actions, inactions or policies of any external
Website/Application.
Children
While the Website/Application may be visited by children, we do not knowingly collect
or use any Personal Information from children under the age of 13 and hereby
specifically prohibit any user under the age of 13 from providing us with any Personal
Information. If you are a parent of a child under 13 years of age and you believe your
child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us at
privatepolicy@konstruktor.com and we will delete the information from our system.
We may collect a device ID or other persistent identifier linked to the device or computer
that may be used by a child to in order to use our Website/Application. The data collected
will be anonymous and not tied to any Personal Information. In addition, this data will be
used solely for internal purposes such as personalization of content, security, and
contextual (not behavioral) advertising.
If you are between the age of 13 and 18, please obtain your parents' permission prior to
registering with our Platform or providing us with any Personal Information.
Cookies
In connection with the foregoing collection of Personal Information and Usage Data, we
may also use cookies (tiny text files that are stored on your computer's hard drive when
you visit certain web pages that identify your computer and may store information about
you) and other technologies to learn more about your preferences on our Websites/Apps,
so that we can improve our services and our Website/Application. From this we may
learn what web pages you visit and which various Website/Application features are used.
The foregoing Usage Data and cookies will not reveal your identity or be linked to you
personally.

Changes
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. In the event we make
material changes to this Privacy Policy, such policy will be re-posted in the "Privacy"
section of our Website/Application with the date such modifications were made indicated
on the top of the page. Therefore, please review this Privacy Policy from time to time so
that you are aware when any changes are made to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use
of the Website/Application after such change constitutes your acceptance of any such
change(s), and if you do not accept any changes, you may choose not to use the
Website/Application or opt out by sending us an appropriate notice.
Websites/Apps Security
It is entirely your choice whether or not you provide Personal Information to us. We
and/or our third-party partners have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial
procedures to attempt to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data
security, and correctly use the Personal Information collected through the
Website/Application. We take, or obligate applicable third parties to take, reasonable
precautions to protect our customers' Personal Information against loss, misuse,
unauthorized disclosure, alteration, and destruction. However, please remember that no
transmission of data over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be
100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot
ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us or from us, and
you do so at your own risk. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information
you transmit to us by email and you do so at your own risk.
When we use third parties to assist us in processing your Personal Information or credit
card information we take reasonable steps to require that they comply with this Privacy
Policy and otherwise protect your Personal Information (including any credit card
information).
If there is a breach of security involving your credit card information from our
Website/Application, we will inform you immediately and take commercially reasonable
steps to rectify such breach.
If you believe your Personal Information is being improperly used by us or any third
party, please immediately notify us via email at privatepolicy@Konstruktor.com .
In the event you choose to establish an account with us, you should not share your login
information with anyone.
Legal Disclaimer
Our Websites/Apps operate AS-IS, and we do not represent or warrant that our
Websites/Apps will be available at all times, or that your use of the Websites/Apps will

be uninterrupted or error-free. We are not responsible for your ability to access the
Websites/Apps or for matters beyond our control. This Privacy Policy is governed by
California law, excluding its provisions on choice of law.
If you have any general questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at
privatepolicy@konstruktor.com
